paulfredrick.com 2017-06-06

# Safety/Privacy Using Your Information | Paul Fredrick

### Paul Fredrick is committed to respecting the privacy of our customers.

The information collected on our site is used to improve your shopping experience and communicate with you regarding Paul Fredrick products. **We do not collect any of your personal information unless you provide it to us.** The information collected includes your first and last name, address, email address, telephone number and credit card information. This information is used to process your order and contact you regarding your order, if necessary. Optional clothing and size preferences are also collected if provided by you. This information is used to contact you about Paul Fredrick products specific to your preferences.

We currently work with partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use Web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing company on this site. The type of information we collect includes product codes and prices for merchandise that visitors purchase, the pages visited, etc. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. If you do not wish to have your visit information used for this purpose, you can “opt-out” by [clicking here](http://www.omniture.com/en/privacy/2o7#optout).

We currently work with a third party advertising partner and its service providers. The information we disclose may include your transactional information with us. Our advertising partner makes the data we provide anonymous and does not use your personal information such as your name, address, email address, etc. This non-personal information is used in order to deliver advertising to you that is tailored to your interests. To choose not to have your transactional information given to, or used by, our third-party advertising partner in this way, you may “opt-out” by [clicking here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**We will not rent, sell or exchange your email address.** A third party is used for email transmission. A blank image is used in individual html emails to track the open rates for email campaigns. If you would like to unsubscribe from our email newsletter at any time, click here.

You may receive a Paul Fredrick catalog if you provide a postal address. We occasionally make our customer names and postal addresses available to select firms. If you would prefer to not to receive such third-party mailings, please contact us by phone at [1-800-247-1417](tel:1-800-247-1417) or by email at [custserv@paulfredrick.com.](mailto:custserv@paulfredrick.com)

If you have registered for a Paul Fredrick My Account, you have the ability to change, edit or delete your personal information online by signing in to your account on the sign in page. Please contact us by phone at [1-800-247-1417](tel:1-800-247-1417) or by email at [custserv@paulfredrick.com.](mailto:custserv@paulfredrick.com) if you have any questions or need assistance with updating your personal information. 

We utilize cookie technology in order to enhance your shopping experience. Cookies are used to assign you a unique and encrypted id when you visit PaulFredrick.com. This id is used if you return to PaulFredrick.com in order to determine if you have items not yet purchased from a previous shopping session stored in your shopping bag.

This site uses Mouseflow web analytics service. The service may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as any text you type in this website, except text in password fields and credit card information. Mouseflow does not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in this website. Mouseflow does not track your browsing habits across other web sites or text inputted in password fields. For more information see Mouseflow's Privacy Policy at <http://mouseflow.com/privacy/>. You can choose to disable the Service by [Clicking Here](http://mouseflow.com/opt-out/).

PaulFredrick.com may match user information with third party data for research purposes only. Also, we disclose aggregate user statistics in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, other third parties and for other lawful purposes.

PaulFredrick.com may disclose user information in order to identify, contact or bring legal action to person or persons causing injury or interference with the property or business practices of PaulFredrick.com or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We will disclose information in good faith when required to do so by law. 

PaulFredrick.com is not liable or responsible for the independent practices and/or privacy policies of other sponsors, merchants, affiliates, advertisers or other persons in correlation with our website. PaulFredrick.com is not responsible for any email transmission problems that would prevent a customer from receiving an email from Paul Fredrick or if Paul Fredrick were not able to receive an email from a customer. 

If any changes are made in the future to the Paul Fredrick Privacy Policy, the date the change was made and a brief description of the change will be listed on our privacy policy page. 

If you are still concerned about your personal privacy, please email your question to [custserv@paulfredrick.com.](mailto:custserv@paulfredrick.com) or call us at [1-800-247-1417](tel:1-800-247-1417).

_Paul Fredrick Privacy Policy effective as of 4/6/2010._

_Privacy Policy updated 4/6/2010. Third paragraph of privacy policy was added._

_Privacy Policy updated 4/8/2011. ClickTale tracking was added to the Policy._

### Security

Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology is used by Paul Fredrick to encrypt your order information. This protects all of your information from being decoded by anyone other than Paul Fredrick. The secure mode begins when you start to check out on our website. 

### Paul Fredrick Guarantee

We GUARANTEE a perfect fit. If you are not completely satisfied, we want to make it right.

Exchanges are free within 90 days, domestic shipping fees waived.

Return it within 90 days and receive a prompt refund of the purchase price.

After 90 days, a merchandise credit for the lowest sales price within the last three months will be issued for any item returned in original condition.

Custom dress shirts cannot be exchanged or returned.

### Contact Information

Paul Fredrick MenStyle  
223 West Poplar Street  
Fleetwood, PA 19522  

### By Phone / Fax inside the U.S. or Canada

**Customer Service:** [1-800-247-1417](tel:1-800-247-1417)  
**Toll Free Fax:** 1-800-713-3512.

### By Phone / Fax outside the U.S. or Canada

**Customer Service:** [1-800-247-1417](tel:1-800-247-1417)  
**Fax:** 610-944-7600

### By Mail

Paul Fredrick MenStyle  
223 West Poplar Street  
Fleetwood, PA 19522-9989, USA 

### By E-mail

You may send an email to [custserv@paulfredrick.com](mailto:custserv@paulfredrick.com).
